speakingathome.com 2017-06-05

# Privacy Policy - Speakingathome

**The personal information collected by SAH will be used for the proper provision of the service and management of the Web. This includes the management of traffic by said SAH for internal management and advertising purposes.**

**The data collected may be transferred to business partners or those contracted for our advertising purposes or notification services, as well as collaborating or contracted companies in the management of the website or of the the service offered, including banks or management of the offered service charges/payments companies and companies that manage third party advertising.**

**Such transferred data will be the strictly utilised as needed, according to the services to be provided by each of these companies or individuals.**

### 0\. Formal express consent

As is stated in the Legal Notice of this Website, Speakingathome Ltd., Identification B87350856, is the owner of the website [www.speakingathome.com](http://www.speakingathome.com/), and exhibits in this section a Privacy Policy concerning the personal information that the user can provide when visiting the Website. 

The Privacy Policy of SpeakingAtHome (hereinafter SAH), seeks compliance with legislation on protection of personal data. In particular, Organic Law 15/1999, of the 13th of December, of Protection of Data of Personal Nature(LOPD) and Royal Decree 1720 / 2007, of the 21st of December, which approves the Regulation of Development of the Organic Law 15/1999 (RLOPD).

As a user of the Website, and through the acceptance of the current Privacy and Data Protection, I am aware and agree expressly that the personal data entered by myself will be stored, processed and used in order to provide the service in a way that is detailed in the Conditions of Use and with the conditions contained in this privacy policy. 

### 1\. Information and ownership of the file

SAH collects data of a personal nature from users and professionals registered on the Websites and includes them in an owned file, whose treatment is exclusively intended for the purpose of managing the services requested and responding to the queries of Users. The Responsible Party for the files is Speakingathome Ltd.

Information received by SAH through their website will be treated with the utmost confidentiality, observing the provisions in force about data protection, and, in particular, the Law 15/1999, of the the 13th of December, of Protection of Data of a Personal Nature at all times. It also adopts necessary measures to, in relation to such data, prevent unauthorised alteration, loss, treatment and access, as well as the duty of secrecy on of the data to be protected and other existing obligations of confidentiality. It also agrees not to use the personal data of the users registered on the websites for different purposes other than, or related to, the contracting of the services it provides.

The user must provide data and personal circumstances required in the registration form to register as a client of the service and/or the payment corresponding to the contract for the provision of services. The registration of such data is mandatory; lack of complementarity of the same by the user or the provision of incorrect data shall entitle SAH to deny the provision of the service at any time. The User or Professional can skip or fail to communicate any data or personal circumstance that is not absolutely necessary to register as a customer or for the formation of the contract.

###  2\. Information Collection 

The Website User agrees expressly that the data and contents entered by said User, or in the record, well within the normal operations of SAH - described in the Conditions of Use-, and of its activity, to be incorporated into an automated file owned by Speakingathome Ltd. 

Additionally, the User consents to the processing of the User's data in order to inform the User, by any means, including email, any changes or developments in policies, activity or products and services of Speakingathome Ltd. or third collaborating companies.

SAH. may use third-party companies to evaluate or monitor with the aim of efficient management of the Website, as well as services or Advertising Websites in order to put advertisements on the Website of SAH or send advertising to Users. Said companies may use cookies or other instruments to measure the effectiveness of our advertising.

At the same time, the client expressly accepts that the email address provided at the time of registration is the contact address to inform the User of acts within the sphere of action of the owner of the file, when the Organic Law 15/1999 requires that they be communicated to the customer.

Also, the user expressly consents that SAH communicate the data as necessary to companies or banks needed for management and/or the payment of the service.

### 3\. Video Recording

SAH, within its services, offers the user the possibility to record classes of that User, although always subject to technical availability of both the TEACHER and the User.

The request for the recording by the student in the form contained in the  Conditions of use involves the express authorization for the storage, treatment and transmission of the data collected by this concept in the conditions contained in the present Conditions and Privacy and Data Protection Policy. 

Being essential for the transmission of the storage of the recording previously mentioned, the user accepts, that if the User requests a recording of this kind, this will be recorded and stored on the device of the Teacher, in order to send a copy of the recording to the User after the completion.

Also, the User expressly accepts that the recording may be promptly and upon notice, stored on servers of SAH and be used for checking the quality of the service offered by SAH, as well as in resolution or investigation of any type of conflict, lawsuit, complaint, claim, or controversy arising SAH's relationships with the User, as well as SAH with its teachers, and between teachers and user.

The user expressly acknowledges that the owner of the file in which the recording is stored is the TEACHER from whom the user expressly requested it and that SAH is not the owner or responsible entity; nor does it have access to the stored data. Therefore, the exercise of the rights that the data protection law recognises, as well as any other type of communication or claim relating to the aforementioned shall be directed directly to the corresponding teacher.

One month following the date of the recording, if there has been no complaint or any claim on a class, the teacher will erase recordings. After which, recovery is not possible.

### 4\. Data: Access, modification, cancellation and opposition

In case of not authorizing the processing of your data for the purpose referred to in the preceding paragraph, the user may exercise their right to oppose the processing by an email with the reference "Data protection" to the email address or by written and signed request sent by certified mail to the following address: 

Speakingathome Ltd., Calle Julio Romero, 12, 2nd A of Móstoles (Madrid),

The same mechanism referred to in the preceding paragraph shall be established for the exercise on the part of the User rights that legally accompany access, rectification and cancellation.

Data collected by SAH may be processed and stored in Spain or any other country where it has facilities. Similarly, non-members of the EU, may carry out international data transfers to countries for what the customer consents expressly, in accordance with the law.

In particular, SAH will provide registered users and professionals a mechanism on the websites to delete information automatically from the files.

### 5\. Security in the information treatment process and data custody

SAH represents and warrants that it maintains the levels of safety for the protection of personal data pursuant to the legislation in force, and has established all the technical means at its disposal to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorised access and theft of the data provided by Users. All this without prejudice to the fact, that the User or Professional expressly accepts that Internet security measures are not impregnable.

### 6\. Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information necessary for us to be able to identify a User during the visit to our Website and during the period of time that is connected. The user's browser stores cookies on the hard drive only during the current session, occupying minimal memory space and not harming the computer. The cookies do not contain any specific personal information and most of them are deleted from the hard drive at the end of the browser session (so-called session cookies).

Most browsers accept cookies as standard and, independently from them, you can allow or block temporary or stored cookies in the security settings.

Without your express consent - by enabling cookies in your browser \- SAH will not embed in the cookies the stored data with your personal data provided at the time of registration or purchase. See use of Cookies

### 7\. Modification of the Privacy Policy

SAH reserves the right to modify the privacy policy expressed herein, according to its own criteria or by reason of any legislative, jurisprudential and doctrinal changes in the Spanish Agency of data protection.

Any change to the Privacy Policy will be published prior to its effective implementation. The mere use of the Website or access passwords after these changes, will imply the acceptance this policy.
